export const LoveQuizQuestions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is often referred to as the 'language of love'?",
      options: ["French", "English", "Music", "Math"],
      correctAnswer: "French"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Who wrote the famous play 'Romeo and Juliet'?",
      options: ["William Shakespeare", "Jane Austen", "Charles Dickens", "Emily BrontÃ«"],
      correctAnswer: "William Shakespeare"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "What is the ancient Greek word for the different types of love?",
      options: ["Philia", "Agape", "Eros", "Storge"],
      correctAnswer: "Philia"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "Which of the following is not one of the five love languages?",
      options: ["Acts of Service", "Physical Touch", "Material Gifts", "Quality Time"],
      correctAnswer: "Material Gifts"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "What is the symbol of love in many cultures?",
      options: ["Heart", "Rose", "Dove", "Cupid"],
      correctAnswer: "Heart"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Who is known as the Greek god of love?",
      options: ["Eros", "Apollo", "Zeus", "Hermes"],
      correctAnswer: "Eros"
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What famous love story involves a prince and a beautiful maiden in India?",
      options: ["Romeo and Juliet", "Layla and Majnun", "Shah Jahan and Mumtaz Mahal", "Orpheus and Eurydice"],
      correctAnswer: "Layla and Majnun"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "What is the traditional flower associated with love?",
      options: ["Rose", "Tulip", "Daisy", "Lily"],
      correctAnswer: "Rose"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "What is the title of Jane Austen's novel about love and social class?",
      options: ["Pride and Prejudice", "Sense and Sensibility", "Emma", "Mansfield Park"],
      correctAnswer: "Pride and Prejudice"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "What is the term for love that is unselfish and selfless?",
      options: ["Agape", "Eros", "Philia", "Storge"],
      correctAnswer: "Agape"
    }
];

  